INTRODUCTION

Dating Online LLC. (“we”, “us” or the “Company”) is committed to respect the privacy and Personal Information of the users (“user” or “you”) in connection with the use of our mobile application and/or by accessing our website [https:/sblocker.app](https://call-blocker.info/) (collectively the “Service”).

Privacy Policy Last updated: 13/05/2024

This Privacy Policy explains how the Spam Call Blocker app ("the App") collects, uses, shares, and protects users' information. By downloading and using the App, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in this Policy.

Information Collection and Use:

* The App may collect and store user phone numbers, call history, and contact information to block spam calls effectively.
    
* The App may also collect device information such as device model, operating system version, and IP address for performance monitoring and security purposes.
    
* The App does not collect any sensitive or personal information without the user's consent.

Use of Information:

* The information collected by the App is used solely for the purpose of providing spam call blocking services to users.
    
* The App does not sell or share user information with third parties for marketing purposes.
    
* The App may use aggregated and anonymized data for statistical analysis and service improvement.

Security:

* The App employs industry-standard security measures to protect user information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
    
* Users are encouraged to secure their devices with strong passwords and keep their software up to date to further protect their information.

Opt-out:

* Users can opt-out of data collection by disabling permissions for the App in their device settings.
    
* Users can also contact the developer at support@sblocker.app or using form at [https://sblocker.app/contacts](https://sblocker.app/contacts) to request the deletion of their information from the App's database.

Changes to Privacy Policy:

* The developer reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time.
    
* Continued use of the App after the changes indicate acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy.

Contact Information: If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the App's data practices, please contact us by [support@sblocker.app](mailto:support@sblocker.app) or using form at [https://sblocker.app/contacts](https://sblocker.app/contacts).
